https://www.msxi.com/en/privay-and-policy/

Skip to content
Privay and Policy
1. An overview of data protection
General
The following gives a simple overview of what happens to your personal information when you visit our website.
Personal information is any data with which you could be personally identified.
Detailed information on the subject of data protection can be found in our privacy policy found below.
Data collection on our website
Who is responsible for the data collection on this website? The data collected on this website are processed by the website operator MSX International Inc..
The operator’s contact details can be found in the website’s required legal notice. How do we collect your data?{7] Some data are collected when you provide it to us.
This could, for example, be data you enter on a contact form. Other data are collected automatically by our IT systems when you visit the website.
These data are primarily technical data such as the browser and operating system you are using or when you accessed the page.
These data are collected automatically as soon as you enter our website. What do we use your data for? Part of the data is collected to ensure the proper functioning of the website.
Other data can be used to analyze how visitors use the site. What rights do you have regarding your data? You always have the right to request information about your stored data, its origin, its recipients, and the purpose of its collection at no charge.
You also have the right to request that it be corrected, blocked, or deleted.
You can contact us at any time using the address given in the legal notice or at privacy(at)msxi.com if you have further questions about the issue of privacy and data protection.
You may also, of course, file a complaint with the competent regulatory authorities.
Imprint
Analytics and third-party tools
When visiting our website, statistical analyses may be made of your surfing behavior.
This happens primarily using cookies and analytics.
The analysis of your surfing behavior is usually anonymous, i.e. we will not be able to identify you from this data.
You can object to this analysis or prevent it by not using certain tools.
Detailed information can be found in the following privacy policy. You can object to this analysis.
We will inform you below about how to exercise your options in this regard.
2. General information and mandatory information
Data protection
The operators of this website take the protection of your personal data very seriously.
We treat your personal data as confidential and in accordance with the statutory data protection regulations and this privacy policy. If you use this website, various pieces of personal data will be collected.
Personal information is any data with which you could be personally identified.
This privacy policy explains what information we collect and what we use it for.
It also explains how and for what purpose this happens. Please note that data transmitted via the internet (e.g. via email communication) may be subject to security breaches.
Complete protection of your data from third-party access is not possible.
Notice concerning the party responsible for this website
The party responsible for processing data on this website is: MSX International Inc.
(Globaler Hauptsitz) One Detroit Center 500 Woodward Ave. 19th Floor Detroit, MI 48226 – Michigan | USA Phone: +1 248-829-6300 Fax: +1 248-829-6030 Mail: privacy@msxi.com The responsible party is the natural or legal person who alone or jointly with others decides on the purposes and means of processing personal data (names, email addresses, etc.).
Revocation of your consent to the processing of your data
Many data processing operations are only possible with your express consent.
You may revoke your consent at any time with future effect.
An informal email making this request is sufficient.
The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed.
Right to file complaints with regulatory authorities
If there has been a breach of data protection legislation, the person affected may file a complaint with the competent regulatory authorities.
The competent regulatory authority for matters related to data protection legislation is the data protection officer of the German state in which our company is headquartered.
A list of data protection officers and their contact details can be found at the following link : https://www.bfdi.bund.de/DE/Infothek/Anschriften_Links/anschriften_links-node.html .
Right to data portability
You have the right to have data which we process based on your consent or in fulfillment of a contract automatically delivered to yourself or to a third party in a standard, machine-readable format.
If you require the direct transfer of data to another responsible party, this will only be done to the extent technically feasible.
SSL or TLS encryption
This site uses SSL or TLS encryption for security reasons and for the protection of the transmission of confidential content, such as the inquiries you send to us as the site operator.
You can recognize an encrypted connection in your browser’s address line when it changes from “http://” to “https://” and the lock icon is displayed in your browser’s address bar. If SSL or TLS encryption is activated, the data you transfer to us cannot be read by third parties.
Information, blocking, deletion
As permitted by law, you have the right to be provided at any time with information free of charge about any of your personal data that is stored as well as its origin, the recipient and the purpose for which it has been processed.
You also have the right to have this data corrected, blocked or deleted.
You can contact us at any time using the address given in our legal notice if you have further questions on the topic of personal data.
Opposition to promotional emails
We hereby expressly prohibit the use of contact data published in the context of website legal notice requirements with regard to sending promotional and informational materials not expressly requested.
The website operator reserves the right to take specific legal action if unsolicited advertising material, such as email spam, is received.
3. Data protection officer
Statutory data protection officer
We have appointed a data protection officer for our company. Datenschutzbeauftragter der MSX MSX International GmbH Hugo-Eckener-Str.
20 50829 Köln E-Mail:
Datenschutz@msxi-euro.com
4. Data collection on our website
Cookies
Some of our web pages use cookies.
Cookies do not harm your computer and do not contain any viruses.
Cookies help make our website more user-friendly, efficient, and secure.
Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer and saved by your browser. Most of the cookies we use are so-called “session cookies.”
They are automatically deleted after your visit.
Other cookies remain in your device’s memory until you delete them.
These cookies make it possible to recognize your browser when you next visit the site. You can configure your browser to inform you about the use of cookies so that you can decide on a case-by-case basis whether to accept or reject a cookie.
Alternatively, your browser can be configured to automatically accept cookies under certain conditions or to always reject them, or to automatically delete cookies when closing your browser.
Disabling cookies may limit the functionality of this website. Cookies which are necessary to allow electronic communications or to provide certain functions you wish to use (such as the shopping cart) are stored pursuant to Art. 6 paragraph 1, letter f of DSGVO.
The website operator has a legitimate interest in the storage of cookies to ensure an optimized service provided free of technical errors.
If other cookies (such as those used to analyze your surfing behavior) are also stored, they will be treated separately in this privacy policy.
Server log files
The website provider automatically collects and stores information that your browser automatically transmits to us in “server log files”.
These are:
Browser type and browser version
Operating system used
Referrer URL
Host name of the accessing computer
Time of the server request
IP address
These data will not be combined with data from other sources. The basis for data processing is Art. 6 (1) (b) DSGVO, which allows the processing of data to fulfill a contract or for measures preliminary to a contract.
Contact form
Should you send us questions via the contact form, we will collect the data entered on the form, including the contact details you provide, to answer your question and any follow-up questions.
We do not share this information without your permission. We will, therefore, process any data you enter onto the contact form only with your consent per Art. 6 (1)(a) DSGVO.
You may revoke your consent at any time.
An informal email making this request is sufficient.
The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed. We will retain the data you provide on the contact form until you request its deletion, revoke your consent for its storage, or the purpose for its storage no longer pertains (e.g. after fulfilling your request).
Any mandatory statutory provisions, especially those regarding mandatory data retention periods, remain unaffected by this provision.
Registration on this website
You can register on our website in order to access additional functions offered here.
The input data will only be used for the purpose of using the respective site or service for which you have registered.
The mandatory information requested during registration must be provided in full.
Otherwise, we will reject your registration. To inform you about important changes such as those within the scope of our site or technical changes, we will use the email address specified during registration. We will process the data provided during registration only based on your consent per Art. 6 (1)(a) DSGVO.
You may revoke your consent at any time with future effect.
An informal email making this request is sufficient.
The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed. We will continue to store the data collected during registration for as long as you remain registered on our website.
Statutory retention periods remain unaffected.
5. Social media
Facebook plugins (Like & Share buttons)
Our website includes plugins for the social network Facebook, Facebook Inc., 1 Hacker Way, Menlo Park, California 94025, USA.
The Facebook plugins can be recognized by the Facebook logo or the Like button on our site.
For an overview of Facebook plugins, see https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/ . When you visit our site, a direct connection between your browser and the Facebook server is established via the plugin.
This enables Facebook to receive information that you have visited our site from your IP address.
If you click on the Facebook “Like button” while you are logged into your Facebook account, you can link the content of our site to your Facebook profile.
This allows Facebook to associate visits to our site with your user account.
Please note that, as the operator of this site, we have no knowledge of the content of the data transmitted to Facebook or of how Facebook uses these data.
For more information, please see Facebook’s privacy policy at https://dede. facebook.com/policy.php . If you do not want Facebook to associate your visit to our site with your Facebook account, please log out of your Facebook account.
Twitter plugin
Functions of the Twitter service have been integrated into our website and app.
These features are offered by Twitter Inc., 1355 Market Street, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA.
When you use Twitter and the “Retweet” function, the websites you visit are connected to your Twitter account and made known to other users.
In doing so, data will also be transferred to Twitter.
We would like to point out that, as the provider of these pages, we have no knowledge of the content of the data transmitted or how it will be used by Twitter.
For more information on Twitter’s privacy policy, please go to https://twitter.com/privacy . Your privacy preferences with Twitter can be modified in your account settings at https://twitter.com/account/settings .
Google+ plugin
Our pages use Google+ functions.
It is operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. Collection and disclosure of information:
Using the Google +1 button allows you to publish information worldwide.
By means of the Google+ button, you and other users can receive custom content from Google and our partners.
Google stores both the fact that you have +1’d a piece of content and information about the page you were viewing when you clicked +1.
Your +1 can be displayed together with your profile name and photo in Google services, for example in search results or in your Google profile, or in other places on websites and advertisements on the Internet. Google records information about your +1 activities to improve Google services for you and others.
To use the Google + button, you need a globally visible, public Google profile that must contain at least the name chosen for the profile.
This name is used by all Google services.
In some cases, this name may also replace a different name that you have used to share content via your Google account.
The identity of your Google profile can be shown to users who know your email address or other information that can identify you. Use of collected data:
In addition to the uses mentioned above, the information you provide is used in accordance with the applicable Google data protection policies.
Google may publish summary statistics about users’ +1 activity or share it with users and partners, such as publishers, advertisers, or affiliate websites.
LinkedIn plugin
Our site uses functions from the LinkedIn network.
The service is provided by LinkedIn Corporation, 2029 Stierlin Court, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. Each time one of our pages containing LinkedIn features is accessed, your browser establishes a direct connection to the LinkedIn servers.
LinkedIn is informed that you have visited our web pages from your IP address.
If you use the LinkedIn “Recommend” button and are logged into your LinkedIn account, it is possible for LinkedIn to associate your visit to our website to your user account.
We would like to point out that, as the provider of these pages, we have no knowledge of the content of the data transmitted or how it will be used by LinkedIn. More information can be found in the LinkedIn privacy policy at https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy .
6. Analytics and advertising
Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service.
It is operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. Google Analytics uses so-called “cookies”.
These are text files that are stored on your computer and that allow an analysis of the use of the website by you.
The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is usually transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there. Google Analytics cookies are stored based on Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO.
The website operator has a legitimate interest in analyzing user behavior to optimize both its website and its advertising. IP anonymization We have activated the IP anonymization feature on this website.
Your IP address will be shortened by Google within the European Union or other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area prior to transmission to the United States.
Only in exceptional cases is the full IP address sent to a Google server in the US and shortened there.
Google will use this information on behalf of the operator of this website to evaluate your use of the website, to compile reports on website activity, and to provide other services regarding website activity and Internet usage for the website operator.
The IP address transmitted by your browser as part of Google Analytics will not be merged with any other data held by Google. Browser plugin You can prevent these cookies being stored by selecting the appropriate settings in your browser.
However, we wish to point out that doing so may mean you will not be able to enjoy the full functionality of this website.
You can also prevent the data generated by cookies about your use of the website (incl. your IP address) from being passed to Google, and the processing of these data by Google, by downloading and installing the browser plugin available at the following link: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en . Objecting to the collection of data{7]
You can prevent the collection of your data by Google Analytics by clicking on the following link.
An opt-out cookie will be set to prevent your data from being collected on future visits to this site: Disable Google Analytics .
For more information about how Google Analytics handles user data, see Google’s privacy policy: https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en . Outsourced data processing{9] We have entered into an agreement with Google for the outsourcing of our data processing and fully implement the strict requirements of the German data protection authorities when using Google Analytics. Demographic data collection by Google Analytics{9] This website uses Google Analytics’ demographic features.
This allows reports to be generated containing statements about the age, gender, and interests of site visitors.
This data comes from interest-based advertising from Google and third-party visitor data.
This collected data cannot be attributed to any specific individual person.
You can disable this feature at any time by adjusting the ads settings in your Google account or you can forbid the collection of your data by Google Analytics as described in the section “Refusal of data collection”.
7. Newsletter
MailChimp
This website uses the services of MailChimp to send newsletters.
This service is provided by Rocket Science Group LLC, 675 Ponce De Leon Ave NE, Suite 5000, Atlanta, GA 30308, USA. MailChimp is a service which organizes and analyzes the distribution of newsletters.
If you provide data (e.g. your email address) to subscribe to our newsletter, it will be stored on MailChimp servers in the USA. MailChimp is certified under the EU-US Privacy Shield.
The Privacy Shield is an agreement between the European Union (EU) and the US to ensure compliance with European privacy standards in the United States. We use MailChimp to analyze our newsletter campaigns.
When you open an email sent by MailChimp, a file included in the email (called a web beacon) connects to MailChimp’s servers in the United States.
This allows us to determine if a newsletter message has been opened and which links you click on.
In addition, technical information is collected (e.g. time of retrieval, IP address, browser type, and operating system).
This information cannot be assigned to a specific recipient.
It is used exclusively for the statistical analysis of our newsletter campaigns.
The results of these analyses can be used to better tailor future newsletters to your interests. If you do not want your usage of the newsletter to be analyzed by MailChimp, you will have to unsubscribe from the newsletter.
For this purpose, we provide a link in every newsletter we send.
You can also unsubscribe from the newsletter directly on the website. Data processing is based on Art. 6 (1) (a) DSGVO.
You may revoke your consent at any time by unsubscribing to the newsletter.
The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed. The data provided when registering for the newsletter will be used to distribute the newsletter until you cancel your subscription when said data will be deleted from our servers and those of MailChimp.
Data we have stored for other purposes (e.g. email addresses for the members area) remains unaffected. For details, see the MailChimp privacy policy at https://mailchimp.com/legal/terms/ . Completion of a data processing agreement{9] We have entered into a data processing agreement with MailChimp, in which we require MailChimp to protect the data of our customers and not to disclose said data to third parties.
This agreement may be viewed at the following link: https://mailchimp.com/legal/forms/data-processing-agreement/sampleagreement/.
8. Plugins and tools
YouTube
Our website uses plugins from YouTube, which is operated by Google.
The operator of the pages is YouTube LLC, 901 Cherry Ave., San Bruno, CA 94066, USA. If you visit one of our pages featuring a YouTube plugin, a connection to the YouTube servers is established.
Here the YouTube server is informed about which of our pages you have visited. If you’re logged in to your YouTube account, YouTube allows you to associate your browsing behavior directly with your personal profile.
You can prevent this by logging out of your YouTube account. YouTube is used to help make our website appealing.
This constitutes a justified interest pursuant to Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO. Further information about handling user data, can be found in the data protection declaration of YouTube under https://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy.
Vimeo
Our website uses features provided by the Vimeo video portal.
This service is provided by Vimeo Inc., 555 West 18th Street, New York, New York 10011, USA. If you visit one of our pages featuring a Vimeo plugin, a connection to the Vimeo servers is established.
Here the Vimeo server is informed about which of our pages you have visited.
In addition, Vimeo will receive your IP address.
This also applies if you are not logged in to Vimeo when you visit our website or do not have a Vimeo account.
The information is transmitted to a Vimeo server in the US, where it is stored. If you are logged in to your Vimeo account, Vimeo allows you to associate your browsing behavior directly with your personal profile.
You can prevent this by logging out of your Vimeo account. For more information on how to handle user data, please refer to the Vimeo Privacy Policy at https://vimeo.com/privacy .
GDPR DSRCCPA DSR
Contact
LinkedIn
Facebook
Twitter
Instagram
Vimeo
Newsletter
